Rising Phoenix is a documentary film directed by Ian Bonhôte.
Elite athletes and insiders reflect on the Paralympic Games and examine how they
impact a global understanding of disability, diversity and excellence.
Self, played by Bebe Vio.
Self, played by Tatyana McFadden.
Self, played by Jonnie Peacock.
Self, played by Jean-Babtiste Alaize.
Self, played by Prince Harry, Duke of Sussex.
Self, played by Ellie Cole.
Rising Phoenix is a 2020 documentary film directed by Ian Bonhôte and Peter
Ettedgui and starring Tatyana McFadden, Bebe Vio and Jonnie Peacock.
The film conveys the stories of nine Paralympic
athletes and their journeys in competition.
The film explores themes of hero, paralympics,
disability, paralympic games, athlete.